I've found out that sound without soul cannot move people's hearts
Ah, feeling it is creepy
Your own face is jerking and being
Cunning that you don't notice
Without noticing that you are thinking worthless
Probably don't notice that you're
Lying to your world
Your face is under layers of masks
What is (the) answer to your life?
You know?
So you let go of everything
Leaving just your mind
Let it go now, free them all
What's needed is your will every time
It's to be honest, yeah
Don't you stop
You take it now
Oh, tear down so many sad bonds
Only you, who can take heart in (the) back of many lies
Don't you stop
You take it now
Get away from biased viewpoints
Call in (your) belief
Lies and lies
Are piled up on my face
That's just like
Invisible shackles that hold you down
Eouh!
Ain't nothing you've done to change
Though you wish and pray so hard
Do you want to change?
Do you really want to change?
What's needed is your will every time
It's to be honest, yeah (It's to be honest)
You just beat it through (beat it through)
(Yiah, yiah, yiah, yiah, yiah)
Now you all, free them
What's needed is your will every time
Don't you stop now
You take it now
Tear down so many sad bonds
Only you, who can take heart in (the) back of many lies
So, don't you stop
You take it now
Get away from biased viewpoints
Call in (your) belief
When it is time
I am going to randomly fire this sound now
The sound that will make you more brave
Tear down the restraints
Take it out with your true smile
With your own true eyes
With your own clean hands
With your brand new heart
Release yourself right now
Don't stop
Gotta go
Gotta get it moving
Lose yourself (yeah)
You stand by yourself
Break your shackle
And laugh at your ease
When you wanna do
Eh-ra, eh-ra, eh-ra, eh, oh
Be free
With your brand new heart
Release it now!
Eh-ra, eh-ra, eh-ra, eh-ra, ouah
Find it out!
Saying what we don't even intend, I was following your lead always
Wanting people to think I really know everything
Saying things not even close to what I intend oh yeah!
[Not noticing noticing the fact, realized]
I could not really find out (realized)
The value of, value of, value of my own life
How can I save myself? (you are) (There should be)
You are, o-oh (a sense that only you feel)
What people think and feel (Feelings)
Shouldn't be all the same (shouldn't be the same)
Do not stop (Do not stop to think)
To feel your will (and feel from your true feelings, yeah)
Say your straight thoughts (Put your straight thoughts and feelings)
And feelings into words (into words and action)
And go, oh (Don't you be so)
Don't be scared and just do it (and just do it)
Cutting out the bullshit
Fuck it up
Saying bullshit
You big Tumblebug
Cutting out the bullshit
Fuck it up
Saying bullshit
You big Tumblebug
Uh, ah (But you)
There might be some moments you (will at no doubt lose yourself and others if you)
Ah (stop to think)
Have to follow people's way out (with your true thoughts)
Pat it! rally, rally! such an
Won't say things outside my thoughts
Won't be flushed
Keep a strong will to fight yourself
Why not be yourself
Uh, oh!
Just know one thing
Don't lose yourself
Everything is worth it all
Saying this is for all lives
Be confident to
Have your own thoughts
And to feel and let out your feeling
Why should there be true feelings you can't say?
We should be
We should be (only what you can feel)
Yeah! (Oh!)
You can find meanings to your existence
You liar
Stop saying bullshit
Look at my eyes and speak
Say what you think or else, you die
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, ah!
Everyday will all be determined depending on your own will that no one (has)
Noticing that I'm doing (the) same things over and over daily
Get out of this loop, find the answer by yourself
I wonder if my own boring life will go on
I just feel everyday is so meaningless
I know I can't be like this
Walking my way home
Once again, "today" is passing by, passing by
Just like today, tomorrow will be the same and will keep being the same
Oh If you do not feel like doing anything, lets go out and get refreshed ah
Though you may have no goals
Then you wait "Alright! Come on!"
My sight has changed on the day (and) moment we (got) going on
It's not the world that changed, (its) myself that changed
I've noticed that today can be changed; its all on me
After all, nothing can be changed unless you make a change
though it may fit in any kind of cases always
Tending (to) run away, it's always my weak self that gets me
Let me change my weakness
Everyone! Right now!
Now Jump! Jump!
As high as you can, Now jump! jump!
No need to think!
The view will change once you jump and jump and jump and jump
It sure is worth to at least give it a single try! jump!
Did you see anything? Did you feel it?
To gain what you all want to get
Those hoping to change "The world (that) surrounds A you" or just waiting
There are no things that will change besides you wo-o-o-uh-o
There are chances everywhere, but in (the) end, you gotta make a change wo-o
Having that in your mind, (get) to work right from this moment
Get yourself out of there now! "Get me out"
Stop wasting time and do it, go on forward towards your dream,
Everyday not giving up like really mad to the best of yours
It doesn't matter if you fail or bite the ground
Say good bye to the usual daily life
Are you all ready to get out?
Do well!
All right?
Dancing floor for you is ready
Step on a step
Don't be so shy (so shy)
Carry on
Dance with us!
Wo-o-o-oh
Stomp hard on the beat
Let's start together
Dive into the bass drums you hear
This shit is still just a damn warm up you know, yeah!
Oh, let us get high now
Oh, let us get extremely high right now
"Damn it, damm it"
She is still not turning back to me today
I can never be honest to myself
I'm about to give it all up after all
The day I was waiting for (It's the day I was waiting for)
The moment suddenly appeared
When I stood on that low stage
You were there in the front row of the crowd
All right
Dancing floor for you is ready
Step on a step
Don't be so shy (so shy)
Carry on
Dance with us!
Wo-o-o-oh
Stomp hard on the beat
Let's start together
I just want to see your biggest smile
Might seem like a dream but it ain't
It is here, yeah!
There are people inside (you just can't deal with)
So it ain't easy to gather hearts to one
Ah!
Fighting since monkeys
And probably will be the same now on
Still fighting just like the ancient days
We are still fighting from ages ago
Ah, ra-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta
Ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta
But here, there is a drip of hope
We-we-we-we, we-we-weh
Making big noise
And we come along with the flow of the noise
And we can become one
There is a small little hope
La-la-la-la, la-la-lah
"Dance tune it is"
We have been hitting the floor from the days we were born
Sound will keep changing
But what we do won't change
We have been hitting the floor from when we were born (It's all the same)
It's all the same since we were apes (since we were apes)
Inside my drawer
There was an old photo
Album with myself all tanned up
Pulling an all nighter, saying
"Going to bed is a waste of time"
At no time, was time enough for me to do all
Here and there, doing this and that
I was always looking towards the days coming along (to the days coming along)
Are you not shooting out your lips with a shit like face now?
Wooh oh-oh-oh-oh!
It must be hot
The backs of those dreaming guys
Do you just want to step back?
Wooh oh-oh-oh-oh!
Words are not needed
Faces tell the story
Just keep running for yourself and life
Here we go it's game time
To fight with all our strengths
Swing your arms hard with all that you have
Wow oh, oh-oh-oh-oh yeah!
The summer party does not end
Age, gender, and all that do not matter
Wow oh, oh-oh-oh-oh yeah!
So let us all have a blast
And let us spend days like going crazy from now on
Summer is filled with innocence
Shaking your neck
To the sound of waves
Dive into this season
Not doing anything soullessly
Spending idle days
Bit by bit damping down
Reach your hands out
Check out those fire works up there
Let's rise up high just like those fireworks
(Just like those fireworks)
Let this heat break up all the upcoming sadness
Let us all get high! Hey!
Let's get high! Hey!
Don't you feel it all coming to you?
Let this heat break up all (the) unwillingness
Let us all get high! Hey!
Let's get high! Hey!
Don't you feel it all coming to you?
Wooh, oh-oh-oh-oh
There you go now
Shout till you are feeling hot and fall forward
Run like mad
Gotta jump
Go Insane
You guys do not notice that we
Are gifted just by being humans
We are absolute predators
We do not even have any enemies
Maybe there are other animals watching us
And thinking that someday "we will beat them down"
Oh we have the brains to think hard
Wear our favorite clothes
We are at no doubt human beings
Many small lives
They were born
with the fate
of dying for someone
A human baby
When will they find out
That at the point they were born, we are
(The) winners of Earth
"Hey, why are you crying?" I ask you, next to me
That's why we live so close together, until we shine
For what have I been living for?
When will I find out the answer?
An answer that is only for you
What will myself and (the) first scenery I saw
Look like?
It's my face, my face
Shut up!
I read this inside the book I read before
[The book I read before]
According (to) Maslow
[According (to) Maslow]
There are five steps (in a) human's desire
To live a long life to stay safe and to receive
[Baby]
love from others
To get respect from
[Baby]
other, To get closer
[Yeah]
to your ideal
That's what it said
[Yeah]
No matter how hard other animals try
they probably can't go over the first step
That is how intelligent we are and, (an animal) filled with greed
But that is probably why we can still live on top of the food chain
in this blue planet although we have weak bodies
Ah, the usual morning reflected in your eyes
Is disappearing in the tears flowing from them
For what to live for
Think deeply as you live yeah
Cuz humans are (the) only ones that can do this on Earth
Your new answer,
What is it that you want to get in your right hands?
Let me hear
Tell me your new answer
Prove that you are different from monkeys
If there is nothing to crave for, humans will die in a way
Don't you think so too?
Let me hear, Let me hear, Let me hear
I'm living (the) same boring shit everyday
Do you really think this is how you want?
We're all here 'cause we know what's fun and not
You don't know anything so
Here we go!
Don't you dare give up!
I got dumped the other day by my girl
But today I'll teach you all (the) fun stuff!
Change this floor to a dancing hall, boys and girls!
Dance and make some noise!
Forget about everything!
Get fucked up (and) scream out with me!
Wo-o-o!
Don't miss it!
(This) time is yours!
You guys ready?
Scream your ass out!
Wo-o-o!
I'll burst your brain in pieces
Close your eyes
Shake your fuckin' head
Don't think of anything
Emancipate
The best moment tend to pass by quickly
That is how life is, life is, waah!
Get fucked up (and) scream out with me!!
Wo-o-o!
Don't miss it!
(This) time is yours!
You guys ready?
Scream your ass out!
Wo-o-o!
I'll burst your brain in pieces
Uh, uh, uh
Looking through the sky (out the) window
Watching the flying birds, I felt jealous
When I saw (the) wet bird on (a) rainy day,
I felt a bit sorry
I admire (the good people)
Because I'm...
Diffident diffident diffident diffident
Check it out now yo
Regretting it turned out like this
Stop it Matching yourself with anyone
It's really silly
So you should have confidence
Oh You are yourself
Facing what only you can do and think
Go and do it right now
Age that everything is things is set, though we are in a blessed environment, some people aren't able to do things
(A) world with too much information
It seems hard to show your real self
Light up your own mind
Find your unique self that you
Oh raised up
Oi Oi Oi Oi Oi Oi Oi Oi
Now are you ready to jump into the world with confidence and eagerness!? Yeah!
当て所なく歩いた夜も 今の僕を支えている
I've started to see the real world
And all my dreams became a goal to me ah
Let us be
(Be able to able to have courage
A talent can't talent can't be achieved without any effort
No such thing as a perfect a person exists in this world)
Why not take a chance of yours
It is almost two point five decades since I was born
I've had so many of jellos so far
And how many more will I swallow from now on?
I've already taken tons of exams
And what else is coming up to me from now on?
Daily lives must pass by quickly without any "likes" and "hates"
That girl who falls for guys easily
Fell for another one then another one and another one each time
For a guy without such experience
Everyday life now is like a stormy river
So fast!
Break out!
I sing to myself before I get sunk
I jumped out to stop the streaming days
The coastline (Shore line I ran)
I ran on that strong sunny day (strong sunny day)
If you wanna take back that feeling (take back that feeling)
That feeling and give it a deep color of your own self
First, smash down that door, yeah
Ah, that guy sitting in the window seat is smart
And that guy two seats away from me
Has such a great sense of humor
And that guy I don't like so much even has good parts
Everyone is calling you too
Just like the others
Just play them out so loud
All those CDs in your room
Have become not attracted to the nostalgic ones
Reshoot those dots
Make yourself into a straight line
On such nights
Have some of your favored
Just trace them
And next reshoot
Tonight, the thunder knocks on your heart
Run hard
And you never know (you never know)
You never know
Never (When the storm)
When the storm
Will come to you
Be strong before
That day (arrives)
Thunder arrives to you (The thunder knocks)
The thunder knocks on your heart
Complete your original sketch of dots
Before that day comes (That day arrives to you)
Aaah (Pon-po-pon-pon-po-pon)
The thunder knocks on your heart
Run hard (When that day comes to you, run hard)
Before that day comes to you ah
Do you think you're gonna be ok tonight?
Ah, feeling awfully lonely, falling down
Oh, thinking what will happen if I'm (the) only one
All alone here in this world
Maybe talking to be free, oh want to be
Uh, alone often recently feeling this
I'm falling down on my own in a muted room as
My lonely feelings keep growing
Everything has meanings for us
And today, I am standing here (By)
And thinking that I am living on my own (his own; I was thinking I was living on my own)
Somehow, oh (A world without anybody does not exist here)
We sure do feel you all
Calling to hear you all
In this life I've lived so far
I saw no meaningless encounters
I want to reconfirm my feelings
Can you feel it now?
Tell me your own way
For now and (the) future
Before my sad daily life
All change into the
All change into the lame old days, wo-oh
And you o-o-oh
To "Keep holding appreciation of" (We want to tell you all)
Thinking that is what's needed (Being grateful for you)
We tend to forget once in a while (At always keep having our gratitude to people)
But shouldn't forget (Gratitude to people)
That is what's important (supporting me; feeling that's what's important)
For a person to live (Though we tend to forget at times)
There is something I wanna tell you all (Always got to remember its one of the things we need to live)
Even now, here, oh (Eh!)
In front of us, we can see
So many people being in our lives
Like this, keeping us one
You don't have be so down (Pya!)
Can't live alone
That is why we are living
And sharing the same world here
"Existing to link and bond"
You, don't bring 'em so down (Pya!)
Why not come out with us?
We want you all to remember
When you feel down
When you've lost yourself
When you are worried about thing
When you feel sad
"You are not (the) only one"
Now and forever
Middle of the journey
Beautiful scene
Terrible scene
More and more sights we want to see
The place we are heading to
And lots more we wanna do
And at the same time we have
The same amount of worries
But are madly into it that we don't feel them
We will keep on moving on and aim high, oh
Our lives will not end up as just a story, oh oh
Not stopping to walk
Until we get them in our hands
Extending our own chances, goal and dream
We want to go over borders
We can get to the end
Gonna really make it come a true one
What people never imagined till now
Gonna make it come true
Nah see you
Past walls that we have faced
Gonna really make it come true
What people never imagined till now
Gonna make it come true, yeah!
Nothing to say
The daily cycle of heading
To our imaged scene (If you have the strong will to get)
If you have the strong will (to the goal to achieve them)
All I can see are big fat walls and my missing factors
All I (There may be times we feel like breaking down)
It doesn't matter if it is time taking
All you have to do is to have the strong will (It doesn't matter if it takes time)
Strong will (All you have to do is to have the strong will)
What we like and want to do
Not missing this chance, oh oh
Holding it tight
We are going to live a great life
We are gonna do it
That is why I'm asking you
Asking you (asking you)
Asking you, oh
Heading towards our "Ideal selves"
Moving towards each goal
Moving to the next when it is achieved (So just keep)
As there is, ah (So just keep on looking)
An ending to a story (and moving forward now)
When an ending comes
(Another) start shows up, oh (There should be a beautiful)
Oh, let us get over (scenery waiting for us)
To the rear end now, oh (rear end now, oh)
Closely listen to the voice and heart beat
Now the beating has stopped can’t hear a thing
Pieces has fell apart
The world we live today is filled with gloom and tears
But what we only can do is to sigh and site alone in the dark
Life filled with vanity
Colors have faded
Things you desire exist here
Flee from this colorless world
Back in the days everything had shined so bright
We didn’t have to carry fear towards future
Dreams colored (and) lit our mind with hope
The sound of heart we shared
Beats in my memory unchanged from back then
Can you hear me sing?
Don’t you be fall in down
Oh, my Lord, it’s gone
What should I do?
Pieces I had
Have fell apart
Where do you belong?
Where should I aim (for)?
Once you’ve lost sight
It’s left to fall apart
Let’s start it over again
Rebuild and combine all the pieces we have lost
To become one
Like a puzzle
Take it one at a time
When I stopped a rusted chain tangled me up
Tying my body onto the ground
As I sink underground I call your name
What can I do to see the day light once more?
Tear it apart and rip it off
Break the chain now
Sink down or swim up
Fight your way through
Seek your way out
If you can not, you are left to drown deep inside
Chain tangled me harder, choking my neck
You who knew all my weakness is gone
Can you come back and stay by my side
I’ll be standing here waiting you
Heart newly born is always strong and brave
No matter how steep the road we take
It can drive us forever and ever
Let’s take it how we want
The choice we make is (for you) and my future
Can you hear me sing?
Misery is nothing
It is all up to your thoughts and beliefs
To bring in success within your life
Don't you compare yourself with other people
That's a waste of person you are, so why not be honest to your emotion?
Don’t you be falling down
All the promises made between us
Broke in pieces and turned into sand
Let's escape from this colorless world to find myself
And tomorrow that we live
I have never gone through such a big love
That you see in movies but
Have been betrayed
And even had beef with people
I had times that I was about to break down
But I found it, "only one"
"Youngness" can't be bought
Even if a billionaire puts down a pile of bills
When a young kid is still a young kid
Being able to meet you gets me excited
Fall into the sky
Oh, gonna dance with you
Taking your hand
Eye to eye
Conveying my love to you, oh oh
Fall into the sky
Oh, making you laugh and cry
So telling you my feelings
Hoping you will be mine forever
Won't let you go
Why are you crying now?
I cannot understand
Oh tell me why, my love
What is making you so sad
Why are you crying now?
Those clear tears will wash my "today" far away
Makes me feel I can't come back
(Wow Wow Wow)
The sound that hits your heart
The words (that) hit you deep in your heart
Beat it now
We wanna dance with you now
The sound that hits your heart
The words that hit your heart
Beat it now (beat it now, beat it now)
Hey you all
Let's jump to the night sky, night sky, night sky (night sky)
I still remember in my heart
The first smile you showed me
Sure sure sure it was beautiful
I don't know how many times
I was saved by your smile
Will keep holding your hand
So just dance tonight (Still remember deep in my heart, the first smile you showed)
So just dance tonight (I don't know how many times I was saved by your smile)
I will keep loving you and keep talking to you (Just dance)
From my heart until the end, yeah (until the end)
So hey you
Here comes the end
The last scene
As I said
I'm not in love like what you see in movie
But to me, your love is movie like
Actually, you are the protagonist, yeah
Hee, hoo, hee, hoo, hee
Uuuh (Oaagh) (Oooh)
Remember
You'll have your feet carried off oh
It is aiming you from the bottom of darkness
Out fine as it always
A sense of worry hits you now
If it's gonna turn out a you wish
Was it turning out so good at first?
No! If you were more careful then, maybe things were different by now
Hey, were there things you could have done?
Don't you be satisfied and push your own luck
Cuz you don't want to sorrow
The hands of the demon could be just around the corner
What will (I) be like 10 years later
Oh Will it turn out just as I want?
Going on so oh
Do the things we want we are glad
But it might all end once you get off track
So we have to keep fighting yeah
Oh everyday, everyday, ah (in) order to keep up this path oh
It's pointless to be depressed
So hear your voice wo-o-o
Don't you be tired Still not enough
So you say wo-o-o
It's important to keep facing and moving forward from now
Never, never, never, never
You will succeed if you keep holding your strong will
Don't you be tired still not enough
Cuz you don't wanna sorrow.
There are numbers of people that want to kick you off from just right there
Ah (The) lose everything all of your stuff, all of your stuff That is what can hit you in no time
Ah To not end up like that, we have to carefully move on now ah
Slacking yourself off could rot you
(You) must not forget that fear if you have a dream that you want to achieve and a place you wanna get to
Always watch your backs for the dark
They are always watching you
Aiming for chance to grab your feet
Once they get you, you can never come back
Kicked down
You sure wanna end up like this?
Short but seems long
Time of our life
What can and will you do in the remaining time
Ah!
Every life of all species aren't eternal
Tick-Tick-Tock
The clock is moving each and every second
Gradually heading to the epilogue
Tick-Tick-Tock
Someday, we will have to face the end of story
Wo-oh
With not knowing how to stop
The second hand will just keep running
Like a sandglass that won't flip
We never can take our steps backwards
Living days twenty-four-seven
Without knowing when our life will come to end
But let's just smile with joy
Time keeps flying
Ah!
We ain't got so long to go
Only a few moment left!
Say if everyday was 48 hours
There would have been more things
We could have done
If our life span was twice as long
There would have been more smiles
And laughter throughout the globe
But clock will tick and gonna not stop
Can you hear the clock ticking
Right inside your chest
Time is life so spend your days the way you want
We have got one shot as who we are now so
Live days with laughter
Lived a day safely basically means
You've got a day closer to death
What goes around comes around
Like life goes reincarnation
Wishing that this moment will last forever is something natural
But unfortunately eternity does not exist for any human
We tend to think back of all
The precious memories
But clocks never wind back its hand!
We all carry fear inside
A fear that this moment
Will reach the end
But don't you cry for now
Though it might be scared
As long as we are alive
We can always come back
Sun arise from the east sky again
And alarms beside the bed rings to wake us up
Time may be flying mercilessly
Leaving and won't let nobody catch-up
But it is not about rushing
It's how you live and deal with your time
Living days twenty-four-seven
Without knowing when our life will come to end
But let's just smile with joy
Time keeps flying
Ah!
Chase the light!
I reached out but I have not arrived yet
I dislike nightly opinions
An impulse to make a convinient excuse
(From) time to time,
I feel like running away
Trying to face away
from this situation
But for me to live
I have to decide my own way
Take it easy
It's gonna be alright
Have faith and
trust what a person you are
In times when you feel lost
believe yourself
Overcome all the enemies
Are you ready? Let's go!!
Chill out
and be easygoing sometimes
That was what you've
told me in bad times
Because I want to laugh when I was about to get entagled
Also check daily days
I can not find it but I will keep my eyes away
I can do it
Stretch out your hand
Fog hanged over
Making me blind(Making me blind)
I cut through the air
with my hand
And then I realized
I ran into a wonderland
filled with mysteries
I knew if I kept
running without stopping
I will someday find the way
out from here
Take a look around
Each one of us shares
different thoughts and features
No one is the same
and that's what makes us
the only special
Spring has arrived
Season of new life has come
So transparent and dazzling to tomorrow
We all face and go
through tough moments
But with the help of others
we gain the power to
stand up again
Why we standing here ?
In such lonely world filled with silence
Why is world so cold ?
We're iced on the ground can't move
Now it is time for me to carry out the promise
The light of hope suddenly shined
We feel the power flowing through us
Why are we so scared ?
We're not alone
Free your emotions and scream from your heart
It rouses now feel that you're alive
Sorry to have you waiting for so long
Would this feeling reach your heart ?
Our heart has been united as one
No one can stop us
This is our destiny
We feel the power flowing through us
Why are we so scared ?
We're not alone
Free your emotions and scream from your heart
It rouses now feel that you're alive
Shake it down
We have confidence to make
You guys guys you guys enjoy
For this day, we have worked so hard
Nobody can stop
No one can stop us
We are gonna make you
All say (we) are the number one! ah!
Your bodies will move once you hear our sound
This place will soon turn into turn into mad(ness)
Make noise, right now, you all
Wo-o-o-oo-o-o-o
Raise your fuck'in voices
Burning Burning soul of you
Ready to get (it)?
Come on right now
Lets go!
Fuck it, suck it
For you to For you to not stop anywhere
We're gonna show you the sound, show you the sound
Nobody can imigate
What we do
Pa pa party night Here is the new sound and new style
Check it out
Yeah Can't be put into any genre any genre
Here is the shit
Sound made in Kobe
Break Down
Hey, you!
Who is looking bored
Imma roll you
In so watch
You are gonna
Shake it now
Hey bring it on
Nothings gonna be
Disturbing
Myself to be proud
Can't be imitating
What is already here.
Something... Looking for
New stuff so
I'm gonna do it now
We are gonna make it, the sound that only
We can beat
Alright,
Now that I'm heere, this
Place is gonna liven up
No one thing is
(Do it)
Gonna stop (me)
We are gonna dye here into our color
Let's make it with us
Bring it on!
(Bring it on)
You and I are (the) protagonists
Party It Up!
Fake ones fuck off
Fake ones fuck it off
You make me sick
Go home and go to bed
Get away
Fake ones fuck off
Fake ones fuck it off
Nothings gonna be
Disturbing
Myself to be proud
Can't be imitating
What is already here.
Something... Looking for
New stuff so
I'm gonna do it now
We are gonna make it
The beat of ours
It's never easy
What we are trying to do can only be achieved a small portion
So we're gonna do it
We are gonna become the
Only one
Open your eyes
And watch us
We are (the) genuine
Let us keep going now
Pay pay attention!
Still not enough, man?
Don't you be so tired Still not enough Party it up oh
Yeah Party it up oh!
VAP
Pa Pa Pa Party night there is the only kind of beat and step
We're not not not
Gonna let let let
You go without getting FUCKED UP
Dancing time
Can't stop us
Further on
We are...
Oh Gonna make you
Shake it now
Yeahh
Don't know what's being misunderstood
Missiles flying
Children getting shot
Swindles everywhere
People who should be
The most loved ones
Killing each other
Once you keep an eye off
Things get stolen
The world is like this
The world we don't know
The unknown world
Out of our hands
It don't matter
Covering it up
Acting like you don't see a thing
If you think it's a defferent thing
You won't notice that the world
You live in is eventually hitting towards this matter
Look at it!
Oh, yeah!
The world is all linked together
Save our loved ones and the world (Hey! hey! Because breaking)
These peaceful days lasting is a wish (down the piled wood castle is easy)
Because I have no idea (Hey! hey! These peaceful days)
How many tickets "to live today" are (left) (continuing is just like a wish)
Even at the time when you were playing cards
Somewhere in the world
Somebody is crying ah (ah, ah)
Us to one
Let me hear your voice!
Oi! oi! oi! oi! oi! oi! oi! oi! oi! oi! oi! oi!
Cmon, Cmon!
Oi! oi! oi! oi! oi! oi! oi! oi!
Ah, eah!
We all have weaknesses
Losing against it is the end
Don't limit yourself
Got to change them, ah!
(Got to change them)
Raise your voice
To fight it out against your weak self
(We sure do gotta change theme, uh)
We sure do gotta change theme
The raising worries
The falling cold sweats on the back (on the back)
Backing off saying
"Can not make it happen" (Breakin' down)
You really think (that way)?
Shake it off and move on (Come on!)
Shake it off and move on
just you are my love
Your pure feeling (You are my love, your faithful eyes)
That beautiful voice
It's so valuable (That beautiful voice It's precious)
I wanna stay with you
Not only tonight (I want to stay with you, not only tonight but from now on)
The words that fell from you (The words that fell from your voice)
Let us change it to connect tomorrow (Change it to connect tomorrow)
Let's sing until our voices die (eh)
There must be many walls
There must be times you will be breaking down
But this song is there for you
There is one thing to tell you all;
Listening to this lively song
"Raise your face now, raise your voice, and dance crazyOh through this night！
" Yeah！Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh
Sing along now！
Loud voice！
You can do (it)！
Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh
(So that) we can leave (the) great moments we spent with ya'll(as memory)
Oh Starry night！
We wanna keep in move, everyone (will) get the best night
Promise you
So shaking' dancing！
Time is now, so shakin' dancing, over your border
Yeah Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh
It's a crazy danceable dance tune！
So don't be late for (it), Come on！
Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh
Here we go！
You all, You all, let's just dance hard！Oh Starry night！
We wanna keep in move and blow your mind again now
We promise you
Shake, so that we remember all (of) today surely
Oh Oh Oh
Party！ Party！ Party！
The best dancing the best playing the best party house isat no doubt...
Oh Regardless Regardless of gender, bounce to this tune and...
Yeah that fuckin dance all night！ fucking dance, all night！
Dance till the dance till the coming dawn
Take a look around you
Everyone that is with you (are) dancing so
Which makes this burning floor
Heat up We are fellows of music
Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh
Find your way out, go forward
When you're about to get into the dark
Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh
Dance, and then you go forward
For your life
Dancing, Shining say Yeah Yeah
Dance all night say Oh Oh
Ah！ Go to the best of you as if you (are) burning your own life
Oh Yeah！ People will shine when they go forward
With their shaking hearts
It's all up to you if you can shine or not, can you make (it)？
Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh
Like a starburst scattering light to the stars Oh Yeah