A person that can't think and do
I'm not one of them, no I ain't
I was totally wrong, yeah
Stop thinking
I'm right, yes I am
Think over as if you are possessed by something
I thought I had it
But I was wrong man
I'm stuck in the middle of nowhere
So I was wrong man
A person that can't think and do
I'm not one of them, no I ain't
I was totally wrong, yeah
Stop thinking
I'm right, yes I am
Think again carefully
As if you are haunted
I thought, I thought I could do it
Is it too late now?
Ah
Reality tells that myself now can not do anything
I can't do anything
Ah
But I wanna get off to a start
Just gotta take yourself in and move on
I want to make a start
Pa-pah
It isn't easy to take in yourself that can not do anything
Have faith to make the right decision, you moron
Ah, Now is the start line
Take in your shitty self along with your tears on your face
There are visions you can see once you begin a new start
There are things you can do once you start new
Get down to zero, right now
Accept your inability
Take down your past self
Do you have the guts?
Get down to zero, right now
Accept your inability
Take down your past self
Do you have the guts to restart again?
What's going on?
How is your face after being crushed down by regret
You were living everyday without knowing, oh
How does it feel
When you believed you were the center of the world
Before I fail
I asked to myself (oh) (myself)
Look back to what you have done and think (look back)
Are you gonna stay (you stay)
As a person who lost heart (who lost heart for others?)
So many hearts in this world that could give you hope
So many thoughts
So many feels
You can see it and you know it
But you don't notice it and feel it
That is why
You are about to end up being alone here
What's going on?
How is your face after being crushed down by regret
How does it feel when you've ignored everyone's thought (oh)
Yeah, alright nobody is here not a single person
I've lost it all myself, oh
I did lie, I did lie but
Never knew it was this tough and lonely!
Hey it's show time (Here we go now)
Music in the woods (Music echoes)
Deers, bears, and birds getting (together giving each other respect)
Hey it's show time (Here we go now)
Now partying with (the ones that they)
Can open up their hearts with (Are you ready to dance?)
Make some noise!
Show me what you got right here
Pump it up
Bring it on with the one you can trust from your heart
Leave it up to our music
Watch the light of sunrise with everyone
Make some noise!
Show me what you got right here
Ah! Awesome music can be heard from the woods once
Yeah, all people with different figures and thoughts
Get together and unite
Might as well wanna listen to a crazy track
So many hearts getting together to make one
We must never forget
That we are all being able to live (being able to live)
There are so many hearts in (many hearts in)
This world (this world)
That are important
This place is filled (filled) with thought!
Thoughts that brought friends (that brought friends)
Thoughts that brought bonds
Thoughts that brought trust together
When you do not notice this
You will for sure end up alone here
You will end up alone someday left behind
Yeah, power of life and death, life and death, yeah
Power of life and death
What're you scared of?
Power of life and death, life and death, yeah
Power of life and death
What're you scared of?
Why not
Look hard at it
There are some that are already there
But some are still trying hard to succeed
Get down (get down)
Though it could be hard
I wanna be able to say
It all depends on you
Check out (check out)
Do you realize your mistakes?
Or do you just blame it on others?
Auh!
Don't blame others
(Don't) blame things
Stop being spoiled
And it makes you wanna achieve
The victory
Shake it (right now)
Success (success) (success)
Or failure is not decided (decided by dice)
It is you (who was born in this world, yeah)
Live or die (live or die)
Live or die all depends on you
Go for it, go for it
If you wanna live (all depends on you)
Pi ri pi pi
Life is fun (life is fun)
'Cause you blame all success and failure on yourself (on yourself)
Not, not, not having the power of life and death (life and death)
For yourself and keep relying on others
Won't satisfy (you when making a mistake)
A-a-a-a-a-a-a-ah
Do you realize your mistakes?
You are stupid
Don't blame it on someone
You know how stupid stu-tu-pid it's to blame it on other pe-people
Don't blame it on something
You know how stupid stupid stupid it's to blame it on things
Don't be a loser
All right everybody
Put your hands up and slap
The side of your ears
Just as you wake yourself up
All right everybody
Put your hands up and slap
I mean, everybody
Let's do it!
Don't end up like shit pa, pa (yeah)
Success, failure (Success, failure, depends on yourself)
All depends on yourself
Stop being Wishy-Washy (ha, ha, everybody)
Don't you shit blame (Don't you shit the blame, commit to yourself)
Commit to yourself right here
At this spot, this spot, this spot
Cuz pain, bang!
Jokers speaking out
What they don't even think
But I ain't got no words for you now
I can't be the one
One to tell you that things
Would turn out perfectly fine
Knowing it won't
Wooh (Stay natural)
Don't let me down cuz
I know you're alright
Wooh (It's no big deal at all)
Don't be wishing things you can't
Ah, (ah)
Be honest to your instinct
You as one
Unique and only
There is no need to change (Tell me ten good reasons why you have to change)
Ah (Get on the car right now and turn the key)
*Don't have to step on the break
Speed it up
*Disc goes round and round
As if on fast lane (Life will not gonna decelerate, why not take it)
Once you turn the key
Grab the handle
You are now
On your own
Where ever you go
Steer right left
Or go straight
Your choice is yourself
If you are stuck
Find whatever you like
And why not
Do all the things you can do
Ride across it
Ride it over
Ah, (ah)
Don't have to step on the break
Speed it up
Disc goes round and round
Like driving on fast lane
Spin the disc faster
Could you come out form the shade
Get under the sun
Try to seek for what you want to do
Wo-oh-oh
Scenery you've not yet discovered
Is all out there
Step on the peddle
Speed it up quicker
Run like the wind
No need to speed down
Wo-oh-oh
Do not care about other people
Who laughs at you and disrespects you
Is the choice you make
And your own aim
Wo-oh oh-oh-oh-oh
Wo-oh Wo-oh
Ooeeh
Turn and grab on to the steering wheel
Keep going; speed it up
Have meters full
Let the engine roar like a mad beast
Get the gears heated
Accelerate
All right?
Dancing floor for you is ready
Step on a step
Don't be so shy (so shy)
Carry on
Dance with us!
Wo-o-o-oh
Stomp hard on the beat
Let's start together
Dive into the bass drums you hear
This shit is still just a damn warm up you know, yeah!
Oh, let us get high now
Oh, let us get extremely high right now
"Damn it, damm it"
She is still not turning back to me today
I can never be honest to myself
I'm about to give it all up after all
The day I was waiting for (It's the day I was waiting for)
The moment suddenly appeared
When I stood on that low stage You were there in the front row of the crowd
All right
Dancing floor for you is ready
Step on a step
Don't be so shy (so shy)
Carry on
Dance with us!
Wo-o-o-oh
Stomp hard on the beat
Let's start together
I just want to see your biggest smile
Might seem like a dream but it ain't
It is here, yeah!
Yeah! Let us get high now
There are people inside (you just can't deal with)
So it ain't easy to gather hearts to one
Ah!
Fighting since monkeys
And probably will be the same now on
Still fighting just like the ancient days
We are still fighting from ages ago
Ah, ra-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta
Ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta
But here, there is a drip of hope
We-we-we-we, we-we-weh
Making big noise
And we come along with the flow of the noise
And we can become one
There is a small little hope
La-la-la-la, la-la-lah
"Dance tune it is"
We have been hitting the floor from the days we were born
Sound will keep changing
But what we do won't change
We have been hitting the floor from when we were born (It's all the same) It's all the same since we were apes (since we were apes)
Was taking it for granted (yeah taking it for)
(The) day ends, then comes tomorrow
(ah yeah, ah yeah, ah yeah comes tomorrow)
Oh, then comes the next day (then comes, yeah)
Spending the day (the day laughing, yeah laughing, yeah)
Laughing with your crew
Talking so-and-so, was great (Hey yo so and so was great)
I've been living so far just for (the) heck of it (Here we go,
so and so was great, so far so far just for the heck)
So there were things I could not notice (Come on)
The common days (days)
The common days (days days)
The usual days anybody would spend (anybody would spend, yeah)
Thought it would continue (days)
Thought it would continue (days days)
Never even thought about (the) fact that
it would all end (It would all end someday)
Oh, someday (Someday I never was, yeah)
I never was bothered to face death in
my life (Bothered to face death in my life)
Oh, oh, you should be able (Oh, you should be able)
Should be able (should be able)
Should be able to do that (should be able to do that, yeah)
End of life lead us to a part of nature (a part of nature)
Someday we won't be able to see each
other the next day, oh (Ah oh, ah oh, say good bye)
And cuz there are limits to time that (Alright alright limits to time)
Makes it meaningful
We can live now facing forward
If the final result is everything
We can say that people just come to life and die
But that's not right
What's important is how we spend a meaningful time now
Ah yeah, yeah, yeah
Feel and express one and two and three and go
Live the limited time, say my name
Let's go
End of life lead us to a part of nature (a part of nature)
Someday we won't be able to see each
other the next day, oh (Ah oh, ah oh say good bye)
And cuz there are limits to time that (Are limits, makes it meaningful wow)
Makes it meaningful
We can live now facing forward
We will eventually die and vanish
Ending up as pieces of ash
Die, die, die
(We won't be able to shout out loud like this)
Won't be able to touch
There is no such thing as eternal youth and immortality
All every single living thing that were born
In this world will absolutely die
The original tracks that constantly plays through the stereo
Sound that's very awesome
Sound that's very alright, that's right
Oh no, the messed up pool table
Oh yes, yummy brunch at twelve, oh
Kei taking off in the middle of the night
Our style of hip hop
Limited life and limited days
What do you intend to do within this time? Yeah
Wanna make it a productive one
We will die (we will die)
We will disappear (we will disappear)
That is why today is great (that is why today is great)
You only live once no (you only live once no)
Choice but (choice but)
To keep moving on
We will die (we will die)
We will disappear (we will disappear)
That is why today is great (that is why today is great)
No other life than this (No other life than this)
This one (this one)
You only live once in forever
Find it out!
Saying what we don't even intend, I was following your lead always
Wanting people to think I really know everything
Saying things not even close to what I intend, oh yeah
Not noticing, noticing, noticing the fact, realized (I could not really find out)
The value of, value of, value of my own life, you are (How can I save myself?)
You are, oh oh (There should be a sense that only you feel)
What people think and feel shouldn't be
all the same. Do (Feelings shouldn't be the same)
Not stop (Do not stop to think)
To feel your will (and feel from your true)
Say your straight thoughts and feelings
(feelings, yeah. Put your straight thoughts and feelings)
Into words and (into words and action. Don't you)
Go, oh (be so oh)
Don't be scared and just do it (and just do it)
Cutting out the bullshit, Fuck it up, saying bullshit you big Tumblebug
Cut out (the) bullshit, Fuck it up, saying bullshit you big Tumblebug
Uh, ah (But you)
There might be some moments you
(will at no doubt lose yourself and others if you)
Ah (stop to think)
Have to follow people's way out (with your true thoughts, ...)
Pat it! Rally, rally! Such an... Pat it! Rally, rally! Such an...
Won't say things outside my thoughts. Won't be flushed
Keep a strong will to fight yourself
Why not be yourself, why not be yourself, why not be yourself
Uh, oh!
Just know one thing
Don't lose yourself
Everything is worth it all, saying this is for all lives
Be confident to have your own thoughts and to feel and (let) out your feeling
Why should there be true feelings you can't say?
We should be... We should be... We should be
Only (what) you can feel oh (Yeah!)
You can find meanings to your existence
You liar
Stop saying bullshit
Look at my eyes and speak
Say what you think or else, you die
Oh, ah!
If we have different faces
So do we have different, different sense of values
Each person's perspective
Each person's stance
Each person's sense of values
Take them in
Just how you and I are different
Each person in the world has what they wanna say
What they value
And what they don't care, they don't care, they don't care about
They are all totally different
In this world that a lot of people live
If what you want is different
So is your sense of value
There may be things you just can't take in but what you gotta do
First is to look straight towards
The person and understand
That's what's important, see?
I've fallen in love with you
So I miss you
But I haven't told that to anyone yet
Never call me "Pop Star"
Actually that's not true
My heart is aching
Ouh!
I could never understand what he's saying
But it seems like everything makes sense to him
He brought 18 cream puffs again today
Yeah! How chaos this world is
In this world, oh
That a lot of people live, ah!
It means that there are that many different sense of values
So let's try to understand each other
You pigs that are not trying to take each other in
And just fighting
Stop the war!
You maggots!
Ah, ah, ah!
Oh, if we have different faces
So do we
So do we have different sense of values
We all live together if you cannot take others in
That is it, that is it
Try to understand lots and take
Lots and take them in
And take them in
A chaotic world
There is no need of pointless dispute
The world you see
Will widen as you learn to take in
The different values
I'm living (the) same boring shit everyday
Do you really think this is how you want?
We're all here 'cause we know what's fun and not
You don't know anything so
Don't you dare give up!
Here we go!
I got dumped the other day by my girl
But today I'll teach you all (the) fun stuff!
Change this floor to a dancing hall, boys and girls!
Dance and make some noise!
Forget about everything!
Get fucked up (and) scream out with me!
Wo-o-o!
Don't miss it!
(This) time is yours!
You guys ready?
Scream your ass out!
Wo-o-o!
I'll burst your brain in pieces
Close your eyes
Shake your fuckin' head
Don't think of anything
Emancipate
The best moment tend to pass by quickly
That is how life is, life is, waah!
Get fucked up (and) scream out with me!
Wo-o-o!
Don't miss it!
(This) time is yours!
You guys ready?
Scream your ass out!
Wo-o-o!
I'll burst your brain in pieces
Uh, uh, uh
Where do I go from here?
Now, where do I head for?
Which way oh is the right way?
Can't find out when you didn't even try
What is really scary is
Not the road at night
Not even a wicked, ah
It's yourself that cannot even feel a thing
After realizing you've lost the right way
You wanna stay right?
Falling down is easier than what you think
Do you understand?
You have no choice but to take the hard way
If you want to stay truthful
Not easy to keep fighting for justice
Since you have to think and know what is right
Every night, every night
You have to keep chasing the right answer (that) always changes so
Oh, every night, oh every night we'll chase
It's hard to maintain what is right
It might be easy if you stop thinking
But I do not think that the easy way (but I don't think that the easy way)
Is the way to happiness in this hard life
that we were all given (in this hard life that we were)
Right way is what you think and find (think and find but I want)
But I want to choose (the) path and way of my happiness (my happiness)
Though in hard waves; not losing, not losing the destination
I want to keep steering towards (the) way I believe (I believe)
It is hard to keep fighting (for) justice
Because you gotta think what is right
You gotta keep chasing
The correct answer that always changes
(The correct answer that always changes)
Answers keep changing
We gotta keep thinking
To find the way we can stay right
Come on ladies and gentlemen!
Hey that's right!
Catch and set it now!
This is what people call us
"Fear, and Loathing in Las Vegas"
Yes Sir!
Let's go for it and follow me!
Don't dirty your clothes with your drive! (auh)
Do you feel the worth of your existence?
A question hits your mind on a depressed night
Have you ever thought oh if there are things that only you can do?
You are the only one!
What is what you can do?
What thoughts you got now to do it? (Yeah! Do it!)
Don't wrap yourself inside a blanket you know
What is what you can do?
What thoughts you got now to do it? (Yeah! Do it!)
It ain't something you can achieve without trying (Without knowing)
That you are drowning down into the mud
Though you diss the ones
(that have managed, managed to pull, pull, pull it off)
You can't admit the fact of yourself
Being ah so cliche? (Watch out!)
Hey stay in the crowd? (Destroy!)
Go out! Yo, come on now with your strong will!
Are you ready, guys?
Find yourself your only self with your silent heart
You are always the only you that will never change as always
Wo-o-o-o-o! Wo-o-o-o-o!
There sure are things only you can do
Cuz you are the only one
Wo-o-o-o-o! Wo-o-o-o-o!
The ones that don't even know left, right, or wrong will shine in life
Go find the meaning of yourself
Yeah!
Do you know your feelings？
Your hearts will be harder to see as you keep living
At least let yourself believe yourself believing that
You are the masterpiece God has made. Alright!
You wanna win this? (Ha!)
Like to be praised? (Ha!)
Really like being praised? (Let's go!)
You are the best players
Come on! Let's get it going on!
Yeah!
So, so, so, so!
Your hearts will be harder to see as you (keep) living
At least let yourself believe yourself
Wo-o-o-o-o! Wo-o-o-o-o!
To live as yourself
It's actually like grabbing, like grabbing the sky
Wo-o-o-o-o! Wo-o-o-o-o!
There are no insane circuits
So that you can move forward in your way, ah
Ready! Run! Dance! Go!
Catch yourself meaning to your life
Think tell show
Cuz there are things only you can
The light will shine as you think your best is further
Wo-o-o! Wo-o-yeah!
Let's get fired up tonight
You need more than 6th sense
At least use thirteen to feel it
Wake up!
Right now and burn it
Stand up!
Your heart is dancing
Dance now!
More than yesterday
Throw that stone with full speed
It isn't easy
To link bonds with people
To polish definite skills
To keep putting yourself into something
For the things you want
It is something that people can not achieve easily, yeah
That is why it's valuable
It's important
To achieve something important
Is like building something little by little
The strength to not lose against yourself, yourself
And the passion to not lose against others is needed
It's something that people can't achieve easily
That is why, that is why it's worth it
Oi, oi!
It ain't something you can get in a day or two so
Skills (that) shakes people's hearts
It ain't something you can get in just a day or two so
The trustable people that are always with you
The strong will of running towards your target
Do all you can do, ah
Hybrid car
Like a hybrid car of heart and body
This is how we function
It's no doubt for people
Who try to take the easy way out to be left behind
The course that awaits him is a sheer cliff
That's what I think, how about you?
Don't wanna end up like him
We are here! Stand up
And let's go ahead
Doesn't have to be cool
It can look bad
We are here! Stand up
And let's go ahead
Cuz there is something to gain after the pains
The sweat you can feel
The troubled times
You spent will mean something to you, oh
The important thing will be seen before what you crave for
The important things
Aren't easy to gain
But your efforts
But your efforts will bring them to you, oh
The irreplaceable things
Gain as much as you can
What will be assets of your life
A-a-a-a-a-a-a-ah
O-o-o-o-o-oh
The troubled times will have its meaning (its meaning)
What's important comes before what you crave
Achieve as much as you can (as you can)
What will be the assets of your life
Ah!
Chase the light!
I reached out but I have not arrived yet
I dislike nightly opinions
An impulse to make a convinient excuse
(From) time to time,
I feel like running away
Trying to face away
from this situation
But for me to live
I have to decide my own way
Take it easy
It's gonna be alright
Have faith and
trust what a person you are
In times when you feel lost
believe yourself
Overcome all the enemies
Are you ready? Let's go!!
Chill out
and be easygoing sometimes
That was what you've
told me in bad times
Because I want to laugh when I was about to get entagled
Also check daily days
I can not find it but I will keep my eyes away
I can do it
Stretch out your hand
Fog hanged over
Making me blind(Making me blind)
I cut through the air
with my hand
And then I realized
I ran into a wonderland
filled with mysteries
I knew if I kept
running without stopping
I will someday find the way
out from here
Take a look around
Each one of us shares
different thoughts and features
No one is the same
and that's what makes us
the only special
Spring has arrived
Season of new life has come
So transparent and dazzling to tomorrow
We all face and go
through tough moments
But with the help of others
we gain the power to
stand up again
Have you ever found one that you just have to keep pursuing?
One, two, three, yeah
A real dream never stops
Getting started
She changed
Seems to have found a dream that she wants to fulfill
Thought she would get bored of anything easily
But this time seems to be different oh (ooh-ru-ooh-ooh-eh)
I can see her going over her limits, oh
No matter how hard of a training
It is or harsh words (it is or harsh words)
Yelled at I can see her, going beyond her borders (beyond borders)
So you ever thought (ever thought) about your dream?
To set your goals and (to set your goals and, yeah)
Putting effort to achieve it
Will bring you an irreplaceable time (bring you an irreplaceable time)
So you ever found (ever found)
One that you just have to keep pursuing? (keep pursuing, yeah)
Seeing a person pursue dreams (dreams is one)
Is one of a stunning thing to see
Brings you a priceless time
Microphone
Imma catch japanese dream with this
Not enough with my family car
Though bad fuel efficiency
American cars are dreamy
Private studio and a huge house
Why (why) not (not) be greedy because (gay gay)
That is what you call a dream a dream
Playing (playing) like (like) this here we are again (gay gay)
Today with a worn out microphone in one hand
Have you ever thought?
What place do you want to be in the future?
Yeah I'm able to see her going above her, above her borders
Despite the harsh words and hard times
I can see her going over her limits, yeah
Going over limits, over limits going over
I can see you (can see you)
Beyond your (beyond your)
Borders despite the harsh words (despite the harsh words)
So you ever thought (ever thought) about your dream?
To set your goals and (to set your goals and yeah)
Putting effort to achieve it
Will bring you an irreplaceable time (bring you an irreplaceable time)
So you ever found (ever found)
One that you just have to keep pursuing? (keep pursuing, yeah)
Such a stunning thing
It's such a stunning thing to have a dream (stunning thing to have dream)
A real dream never stops and (So you ever found one that you just have to keep pursuing?)
Your heart never stops so (wo-oh-oh-oh)
Might as well go for a big one (such a stunning thing, such a stunning thing to have a dream, yeah)
Live with dream, yeah
A real dream never stops and (So you ever found one that you just have to keep pursuing?)
Your heart never stops
Live with a dream
Might as well go for a big one
Go and find a dream of your life
Your life work
I don't know what's being misunderstood
Missiles flying
Children are getting shot
Swindles everywhere
People who should be
The most loved ones
Killing each other
Once you keep an eye off
Things get stolen
The world is like this. The world we don't know
The unknown world out of our hands
It don't matter. Covering it up
Acting like you don't see anything
If you think it's a different thing
You won't notice that the world
You live in is eventually hitting towards this matter
Look at it!
Oh, yeah!
The world is all linked together
Save our loved ones and the world (Hey! Hey! Because breaking)
These peaceful days lasting is a wish (down the piled wood castle is easy)
Because I have no idea (Hey! Hey! These peaceful days)
How many tickets to live today are left (continuing is just like a wish)
Oh, even at the time when you were playing cards
Somewhere in the world
Somebody is crying (ah, ah)
Us to one
Let me hear your voice!
Oi! oi! oi! oi!...
Ah, eah!
We all have weaknesses
Losing against it is the end
Don't limit yourself
Don't limit yourself, yeah!
Got to change them!
Raise your voice
To fight it out against your weak self
(We sure do gotta change theme, uh)
We do gotta change theme
The raising worries
The falling cold sweats on the back (on the back)
Backing off saying
"Can not make it happen" (breakin' down)
You really think (that way)?
Shake it off and move on (come on!)
Shake it off and move on
Just you are my love
Your pure feeling (you are my love, your faithful eyes)
Your beautiful voice
It's so valuable (your beautiful voice, it's so precious)
I wanna stay with you Not only tonight, uh
(I want to stay with you, not only tonight but from now on)
The words that fell from you (the words that fell from your voice)
Let us change it to connect tomorrow (change it to connect tomorrow)
Let's sing until our voices die
Oh, there must be many walls
There must be times you will be breaking down
But this song is there for you
He said, "If you wanna talk about your ideal
You need power that corresponds with it"
Not even having an ideal to talk about
That day, I just gave it up
But seeing people living hard, getting heat from their ambitions
Can't stay as who I am now who can't think of
A sin-sin-sin-sin-single thing to win
Time to move now
I want to achieve it, that is why I have to
Do what it takes with this hand, changing
The length of this feelings to the amount of heat
I'm gonna achieve it regardless of its size
I want to achieve it, I want to achieve it, I want to achieve it
Changing the length of this feelings to the amount of heat
I'm gonna achieve it no matter how big it is
You done already？
Don't you wanna win what you hoped for with your own hands？
Then go for it with your strong heart and show it to me right here
You pigs
If you can't, then we're done talking
Alright, do your best and cry out loud, you pigs! Yeah
Don't you stop even if you cannot see what is in front of you
If you can't, then we are done talking
Do your best and cry out loud, keep the heat and fire yourself up
Keep on going single minded
You done already?
Seeing people filled with ambition
Getting heat from the power to achieve something big
Can't stay as who I am now
Who can't think of a single, single, single thing to win
Time to move now
I want to achieve it, so whatever it takes
What's needed is to try hard with my hands
To get one in this hand
I believe (to achieve a big one)
That is where (you need to put that much guts into it)
You can find (a big foot print to this generation)
What's really worth (let us stomp it, yeah)
You guys do not notice that we
Are gifted just by being humans
We are absolute predators
We do not even have any enemies
Maybe there are other animals watching us
And thinking that someday "we will beat them down"
Oh we have the brains to think hard
Wear our favorite clothes
We are at no doubt human beings
Many small lives
They were born
with the fate
of dying for someone
A human baby
When will they find out
That at the point they were born, we are
(The) winners of Earth
"Hey, why are you crying?" I ask you, next to me
That's why we live so close together, until we shine
For what have I been living for?
When will I find out the answer?
An answer that is only for you
What will myself and (the) first scenery I saw
Look like?
It's my face, my face
Shut up!
I read this inside the book I read before
[The book I read before]
According (to) Maslow
[According (to) Maslow]
There are five steps (in a) human's desire
To live a long life to stay safe and to receive
[Baby]
love from others
To get respect from
[Baby]
other, To get closer
[Yeah]
to your ideal
That's what it said
[Yeah]
No matter how hard other animals try
they probably can't go over the first step
That is how intelligent we are and, (an animal) filled with greed
But that is probably why we can still live on top of the food chain
in this blue planet although we have weak bodies
Ah, the usual morning reflected in your eyes
Is disappearing in the tears flowing from them
For what to live for
Think deeply as you live yeah
Cuz humans are (the) only ones that can do this on Earth
Your new answer,
What is it that you want to get in your right hands?
Let me hear
Tell me your new answer
Prove that you are different from monkeys
If there is nothing to crave for, humans will die in a way
Don't you think so too?
Let me hear, Let me hear, Let me hear
The old way I saw in my dream
The kids talking about what to do now
With shining eyes
Closing my eyes
I am alone in the coldness
Ah-ah!
Feeling really down
Ah-ah-ah-ah!
Losing all the meaning to live
E-yeah!
Knowing it's not right
Oh-oh-oh!
Can't put my energy against it
The cold winter has passed by
Come on! Let us go to
The school route filled with cherry blossoms
A place kids are still hanging out, yeah
Before it's over
Dance like those petals waving in the breeze
Free your frozen self seized in fear
You know the view of the cherry blossoms
(The scene of the cherry blossoms)
Let me send you the view along with my voice
(Let me send the scene to you)
Take the memory to heart, and let's face (em)
All tomorrow, don't worry
There should be means to the place
You were raised, and the people
You met there
It really means a lot to me
Where are we heading towards?
What are we going to live and die for?
Reflecting on the tears, efforts, and regrets
Find the answer, if we live our lives today (to)
The best
The light pink petals
Don't you wanna flutter big if you're eventually
Gonna scatter apart?
For it is over
(We have to step hard)
Achieve the power to beat yourself
Come on, here, grab this hand
Everyone is scared
(Everyone is scared, everyone is a coward, so let us step now)
So let us step on the steps together
Starting slowly tonight
And at last, dance hard
Is that all you have got?
Yeah, it's quite tough, though
One more try
Not easy
Alright If you're
Ok with that
Who you think I am?
Ready go!
Say good bye to yourself
Feels like running away uh, oh oh
When the one last step is heavy, oh oh
Hey yo!
That's when you go for it
Say good bye to yourself
Who feels like running away at hard times
When the one last step is dramatically heavy
That is when you go for it
"Go beyond your limits"
That's what they say
Can't do it, oh
At hard times
When I wanna cry
Don't wanna
Don't wanna give it up no more
If the hardest last step
Is the step that will change you
Then do what ever you can do
Take the step
It's not only you who is thrown into a battlefield
That goes for everybody
Everyone living are fighting just like this
I myself will keep fighting, fighting, fighting as well
Yeah! Filled with frustration
Can't help gnashing your teeth every night
Though you've lost your 10 out of 14
Of your top teeth!
Oh, one thing I am glad to have realized
Is the fact that
Oh, everyone is here with me
It means I don't have to keep
Fighting by myself
The fact that everyone (everyone)
Living in the same generation is standing pain (standing pain)
And in the same battlefield (oh, oh, oh, oh)
It probably means a lot
To take the most painful step, painful step, painful step
Which your legs are about to tear off
Everyone living are fighting
Just like this
I myself will keep
I myself will keep fighting as well
Let's go beyond our borders
Stand up!
Why we standing here
In such lonely world filled with silence?
Why is world so cold?
We're iced on the ground, can't move
(Now it is time for me to carry out the promise
The light of hope suddenly shined)
We feel the power flowing through us
(Don't be so scared)
Why are we so scared?
We're not alone (We are not alone)
Free your emotions and
scream from your heart (Scream from your heart)
It rouses now, feel that you're alive
Sorry to have you waiting for so long...
Would this feeling reach your heart?
(Our heart has been united as one No one can stop us)
This is our destiny!
We feel the power flowing through us
(Don't be so scared)
Why are we so scared?
We're not alone (We are not alone)
Free your emotions and scream from your heart
(Scream from your heart)
It rouses now, feel that you're alive!
Road stretches to all directions
North, East, and South, West
It goes on and on and forever
Simple but yet complicated
Tangles and untangles
Life is like a walkway
It goes awfully smooth sometimes but goes tough
Just like how a road goes up and down, right and left
Life goes on in different directions
Stretches perfectly straight
Crosses over in time to time
Signals guides us what to do and not to
But there aren't signals in our life
It's up to us to discover as an individual man
What is right and wrong (in course of life)
There is nothing called short cuts in our life
It's the small steps that pile up
And makes us a better man
You can walk towards left, right, or straight
You can walk anywhere anytime
But not backwards
Eeeeh, Ahhh!
Aaaah, Ohhh!
Ahhh, uah!
On a crossroad
We tend to bump into each other
Fight, fight, fight with many people
Laps, laps, laps over many roads
Just keep walking
If you don't stop someday we
Will, will will achieve what we've aimed
Take, take, take the upcoming chance
So we go
Life and road in many ways (ta-ta-ta)
Interacting with others
Laughing, fighting, and crying
We crossover (ta-ta-ta)
Ah, ta-ta-ta-ta, ta-ta-ta-ta, ouaah
Closely listen to the voice and heart beat
Now the beating has stopped can’t hear a thing
Pieces has fell apart
The world we live today is filled with gloom and tears
But what we only can do is to sigh and site alone in the dark
Life filled with vanity
Colors have faded
Things you desire exist here
Flee from this colorless world
Back in the days everything had shined so bright
We didn’t have to carry fear towards future
Dreams colored (and) lit our mind with hope
The sound of heart we shared
Beats in my memory unchanged from back then
Can you hear me sing?
Don’t you be fall in down
Oh, my Lord, it’s gone
What should I do?
Pieces I had
Have fell apart
Where do you belong?
Where should I aim (for)?
Once you’ve lost sight
It’s left to fall apart
Let’s start it over again
Rebuild and combine all the pieces we have lost
To become one
Like a puzzle
Take it one at a time
When I stopped a rusted chain tangled me up
Tying my body onto the ground
As I sink underground I call your name
What can I do to see the day light once more?
Tear it apart and rip it off
Break the chain now
Sink down or swim up
Fight your way through
Seek your way out
If you can not, you are left to drown deep inside
Chain tangled me harder, choking my neck
You who knew all my weakness is gone
Can you come back and stay by my side
I’ll be standing here waiting you
Heart newly born is always strong and brave
No matter how steep the road we take
It can drive us forever and ever
Let’s take it how we want
The choice we make is (for you) and my future
Can you hear me sing?
Misery is nothing
It is all up to your thoughts and beliefs
To bring in success within your life
Don't you compare yourself with other people
That's a waste of person you are, so why not be honest to your emotion?
Don’t you be falling down
All the promises made between us
Broke in pieces and turned into sand
Let's escape from this colorless world to find myself
And tomorrow that we live
Shake it down
We have confidence to make
You guys guys you guys enjoy
For this day, we have worked so hard
Nobody can stop
No one can stop us
We are gonna make you
All say (we) are the number one! ah!
Your bodies will move once you hear our sound
This place will soon turn into turn into mad(ness)
Make noise, right now, you all
Wo-o-o-oo-o-o-o
Raise your fuck'in voices
Burning Burning soul of you
Ready to get (it)?
Come on right now
Lets go!
Fuck it, suck it
For you to For you to not stop anywhere
We're gonna show you the sound, show you the sound
Nobody can imigate
What we do
Pa pa party night Here is the new sound and new style
Check it out
Yeah Can't be put into any genre any genre
Here is the shit
Sound made in Kobe
Break Down
Hey, you!
Who is looking bored
Imma roll you
In so watch
You are gonna
Shake it now
Hey bring it on
Nothings gonna be
Disturbing
Myself to be proud
Can't be imitating
What is already here.
Something... Looking for
New stuff so
I'm gonna do it now
We are gonna make it, the sound that only
We can beat
Alright,
Now that I'm heere, this
Place is gonna liven up
No one thing is
(Do it)
Gonna stop (me)
We are gonna dye here into our color
Let's make it with us
Bring it on!
(Bring it on)
You and I are (the) protagonists
Party It Up!
Fake ones fuck off
Fake ones fuck it off
You make me sick
Go home and go to bed
Get away
Fake ones fuck off
Fake ones fuck it off
Nothings gonna be
Disturbing
Myself to be proud
Can't be imitating
What is already here.
Something... Looking for
New stuff so
I'm gonna do it now
We are gonna make it
The beat of ours
It's never easy
What we are trying to do can only be achieved a small portion
So we're gonna do it
We are gonna become the
Only one
Open your eyes
And watch us
We are (the) genuine
Let us keep going now
Pay pay attention!
Still not enough, man?
Don't you be so tired Still not enough Party it up oh
Yeah Party it up oh!
VAP
Pa Pa Pa Party night there is the only kind of beat and step
We're not not not
Gonna let let let
You go without getting FUCKED UP
Can't stop us
Further on
We are...
Oh Gonna make you
Shake it now
Yeahh
Yeah
There are lots of decisions we have to make as we live
Ah, ah
We are made from the decisions we make
Ourselves right now are at the top of the road we have come through
The road that you chose has lead you to yourself; what you are
Though the road of decision may be a tough one
Don't you have an ideal self? Ideal self?
Hang tight and pick it out
Now the road you have made with courage will surely be valuable one
Yeah
There are lots of decisions we have to make as we live
Ah, ah
We are made from the decisions we make
Ourselves right now are at the top of the road we have come through
The steps have made you what you are
Pick it out with guts
The road may be steep but
The one you got to be choosing the one you need guts
Oh
You'll see change from what you were before
You might be running away at last
Making excuses
You might just be acting as if you've made the best decision
There are days when you get lost, ah
Always being confronted with the questions
"How do you wanna proceed?"
"What do you wanna do?"
Can you do it? To walk this uneasy road
Show it to me now, do it right now
Yeah!
Go over this tough steep road
Because the future you hope for is there
Have the strong heart.
The strong will to choose the road that you will need courage to
Ah
Pick it out with courage
The road may be steep but
Oh
We're made from the decisions we make (oh)
Ourselves right now are the top of the road we have come through
You might just be acting as if you've made the best decisions
Though it may seem like a steep and tough road, oh
I believe there will be another new dawn in front of me
I want to witness the awesome morning glow
In which we can say everything was worth it
Ah!
There are lots of decisions we have to make as we live